<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jamore Fanpage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jamore Fanpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:07:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Six Afraid of Seven? Six Hasn’t Been the Same Since He Left Vietnam</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vietnam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vietnam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why is six afraid of seven?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Six hasn&amp;rsquo;t been the same since he left Vietnam. He can seldom close his eyes without opening them again at fear of Charlies lurking in the jungle trees. Not that you could ever see the bastards, mind you. They were swift, and they knew their way around the jungle like nothing else. He remembers the looks on the boys&amp;rsquo; faces as he walked into that village and&amp;hellip; oh, Jesus. The memories seldom left him, either. Sometimes he&amp;rsquo;d reminisce - even hear - Tex&amp;rsquo;s southern drawl. He remembers the smell of Brooklyn&amp;rsquo;s cigarettes like nothing else. He always kept a pack of Lucky&amp;rsquo;s with him. The boys are gone, now. He knows that; it&amp;rsquo;s just that he forgets, sometimes. And, every now and then, the way that seven looks at him with avid concern in his eyes&amp;hellip; it makes him think. Sets him on edge. Makes him feel like he&amp;rsquo;s back there&amp;hellip; in the jungle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among Us Is Ruining My Fucking Life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/among-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/among-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t fucking take it any more. Among Us has singlehandedly ruined my life. The other day my teacher was teaching us Greek Mythology and he mentioned a pegasus and I immediately thought &amp;lsquo;Pegasus? more like Mega Sus!!!!&amp;rsquo; and I&amp;rsquo;ve never wanted to kms more. I can&amp;rsquo;t look at a vent without breaking down and fucking crying. I can&amp;rsquo;t eat pasta without thinking &amp;lsquo;IMPASTA??? THATS PRETTY SUS!!!!&amp;rsquo; Skit 4 by Kanye West. The lyrics ruined me. A Mongoose, or the 25th island of greece. The scientific name for pig. I can&amp;rsquo;t fucking take it anymore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It Was a Real Life Gamer Girl</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gamer-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gamer-girl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So the other day, I was playing rainbow six siege, and I heard one of my teammates make a callout in the voice chat. It was a real life gamer girl. God, I kid you not, I just stopped playing and pulled my dick out. “fuck, Fuck!” I was yelling in voice chat. I just wanted to hear her voice again. “Please,” I moaned. But she left the lobby. I was crying and covered in my own cum, but I remembered that I could find recent teammates in the ubiplay friends tab. I frantically closed down siege and opened the tab, to find out she had TTV IN HER NAME!!! She was streaming, and only had 100 viewers!!! The competition was low, so I made the first move and donated my months rent to her. I was already about to pre. She read my donation in the chat. God this is the happiest I’ve been in a long time. I did a little research, and found out where she goes to school, but I am a little nervous to talk to her in person, and need support. Any advice before my Uber gets to her middle school?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who’s Joe? Joe Momma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/joe-mama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/joe-mama/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Who’s joe?&amp;rdquo; a distant voice asks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instantly everyone nearby hears the sound of 1,000s of bricks rapidly shuffling towards his location.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The earth itself seemed to cry out in agony, until finally the ground itself split open and a horrific creature crawled from the ground, covered in mucus and tar.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;”Joe Momma…” the creature whispered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The man cried out in pain as he disintegrated into dust, and the whole world fell silent in fear.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Fucked up DVD</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tight-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tight-hole/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earlier today I was really horny, and I saw what I thought to be a blank DVD. I thought, DVDs have a tight hole, they might feel pretty good. So I put my soft pp into the hole of the DVD, and for a few seconds as I started getting harder, it felt pretty good, but then, once I was fully erect, it started being painful. My pp was stuck in the DVD, and I had to break it in half to get if out. It was then when I flipped the broken DVD over and realized that it was not a blank DVD, but a copy of the Pixar movie Up.. Well guys, guess I fucked up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do I Get My Husband to Stop Going ‘Goblin Mode’ During Sex?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/goblin-mode-during-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/goblin-mode-during-sex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TLDR; My husband says ‘Goblin Mode activated’ when we start to have sex, growls and acts like a caveman, and then says ‘Goblin Mode off’ when we stop, and then pretends not to remember afterward.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I really love my husband and he’s always been great in bed. But recently he’s been acting really weird. So, a couple of days ago, my son went on a rampage through our house and said he was in ‘Goblin Mode’. We didn’t really know what to do with him, so we sent him to live with my parents so he can go to a special needs school. My husband a really great relationship with our son and loved him more than anything. Naturally, he was upset when he had to leave. He’s an incredibly tough man, but this was the first time I’ve ever seen him cry. I think since then, he’s been a little emotionally unwell. I’ve heard him muttering, ‘Goblin’ repeatedly when he didn’t notice me, staring blankly into his food, and just going alone by himself to do who knows what. I feel awful for him, but we both agreed that this was for the best. Last night, the day after our son went away, we decided to have sex to relieve our stress. However, my husband said ‘Goblin Mode activated’, starting growling, and went wild having sex with me. Admittedly, it was some of the best and most experimental sex I’ve ever had, but I’m worried that something might be going on with my husband. Any advice?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Like to Creep Around My Home and Act Like a Goblin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/act-like-a-goblin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 01:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/act-like-a-goblin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t know why but I just enjoy doing this. Maybe it’s my way of dealing with stress or something but I just do it about once every week. Generally I’ll carry around a sack and creep around in a sort of crouch-walking position making goblin noises, then I’ll walk around my house and pick up various different “trinkets” and put them in my bag while saying stuff like “I’ll be having that” and laughing maniacally in my goblin voice (“trinkets” can include anything from shit I find on the ground to cutlery or other utensils). The other day I was talking with my neighbours and they mentioned hearing weird noises like what I wrote about and I was just internally screaming the entire conversation. I’m 99% sure they don’t know it’s me but god that 1% chance is seriously weighing on my mind.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 01:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;this-website-is-cancer&#34;&gt;This Website is Cancer&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISCLAIMER&lt;/strong&gt;: This website and all of its content are intended solely for parody, satire, and entertainment purposes. The materials presented herein are not to be interpreted as factual statements, endorsements, or expressions of genuine opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The creators and contributors of this site do not support, condone, or agree with any of the views, opinions, or statements that may appear in the content. All characters, names, and situations — even those based on real people or events — are used in a humorous or exaggerated manner.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
